clubworldranking.com 2019-06-09

# Privacy | Football World Rankings

Football World Rankings B.V. ([info@clubworldranking.com](mailto:info@clubworldranking.com)) processes personal data that you provide to us by using our services and/or by providing them to us yourself.

An overview of the personal data we process:  

  * First and/or last name  

  * E-mail address  

  * Information about activity on our website  

  * Internetbrowser and device type  

  * IP address (only after cookie acceptance)   

## Why we need data

Football World Rankings B.V. processes your data for the following purposes: to provide you with information by e-mail or download, if you have requested us by means of the contact form.

## Privacy

Football World Rankings B.V. respects the privacy of all users of its site and ensures that the personal information you provide is treated confidentially.  
Football World Rankings B.V. will not store your personal data longer than is strictly necessary to achieve the purposes for which your data is collected.  
Football World Rankings B.V. does not provide information to third parties, only if this is necessary for the execution of an agreement with you or to comply with a legal obligation.  

## Mapping website visit

Football World Rankings B.V. uses only technical and functional cookies. In addition, Football World Rankings B.V. uses analytical cookies that do not infringe your privacy.CookiesFor a full explanation on cookies, see under Cookies Policy.  

## View, modify or delete data

You have the right to view, correct or delete your personal data. You can send a request for access, correction or deletion to [info@clubworldranking.com](mailto:info@clubworldranking.com).In order to ensure that the request for access has been made by you, we ask you to send a copy of your identity document with the request. We ask you to blacken your passport photo and citizen service number (CSN) in this copy. This is to protect your privacy. Football World Rankings B.V. will respond to your request as soon as possible, but within four weeks.  

## Security

Football World Rankings B.V. takes the protection of your data seriously and takes appropriate measures to prevent misuse, loss, unauthorized access, unwanted disclosure and unauthorized modification. If you have the impression that your data is not secure or that there are indications of abuse, please contact us at info@clubworldranking.com.   

## Cookies Policy 

Football World Rankings B.V. ([info@clubworldranking.com](mailto:info@clubworldranking.com)) uses cookies on www.clubworldranking.com (the "Service"). By using the Service, you consent to the use of cookies. Our Cookies Policy explains what cookies are, how we use cookies, how third-parties we may partner with may use cookies on the Service, your choices regarding cookies and further information about cookies.  

## What are cookies

Cookies are usually a string of numbers and/or letters that a website transfers to your hard drive. The cookies enable the website to “remember” you, either for the duration of your visit (session cookies) or for repeat visits (persistent cookies). We recommend that you visit the websites [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and [www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/) if you would like in-depth information about cookies.  

## How Football World Rankings uses cookies

When you use and access the Service, we may place a number of cookies files in your web browser. We use cookies for the following purposes: to enable certain functions of the Service, to provide analytics, to store your preferences, to enable advertisements delivery, including behavioral advertising. We use both session and persistent cookies on the Service and we use different types of cookies to run the Service.  

## Third-party cookies

In addition to our own cookies, we may also use various third-parties cookies to report usage statistics of the Service, deliver advertisements on and through the Service, and so on.  

## What are your choices regarding cookies

If you'd like to delete cookies or instruct your web browser to delete or refuse cookies, please visit the help pages of your web browser. Please note, however, that if you delete cookies or refuse to accept them, you might not be able to use all of the features we offer, you may not be able to store your preferences, and some of our pages might not display properly. If you register with us or if you continue to use our site, you agree to our use of cookies.
